mthink.com 2012-11-07

# Privacy Policy | mThink.com

Thank you for visiting mThink.com, and it's partner Websites. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at this site. _Click h_ _e_ _re_ for a list of the mThink sites governed by this Privacy Notice.

**The Information We Collect**

At some mThink sites, you may be able to add blog posts, order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, occupation/job title; email address; telephone number; fax number; credit card information; and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services.

At some mThink sites, you can submit information about other people. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, occupation/job title, email address and telephone number.

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

**How We Use the Information**

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when you have won one of our contests or in some circumstances, to notify you when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us.

In terms of the information that you provide about others, we may use this information to offer our products, programs or services to them.

The information we collect in connection with our  blogs, videos, online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs or services.

We will disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request.

Agents and contractors of mThink who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for mThink.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. Inadvertent disclosures may result, for example, when third parties misrepresent their identities in asking the site for access to personally identifiable information about themselves for purposes of correcting possible factual errors in the data.

mThink may disclose personally identifiable information that you have submitted about yourself or about others to companies not owned by mThink who want to market products or services to you. For instructions on how to opt out from such disclosures, please read instructions below.

mThink may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, please read instructions on how to make your request below.

Finally, mThink sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

**Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites and Sponsors**

Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

mThink sites may offer contests, sweepstakes or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes or promotion. mThink has no control over the third-party sponsors' use of this information. The mThink site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if third-party sponsors will obtain such information.

**Cookies**

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our Web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your email address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs or services.

**Our Commitment to Security**

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access or Correct Information**

For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that this site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please [click here](mailto:info@mthink.com).

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How to Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns about the mThink online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [info@mthink.com](mailto:info@mthink.com.com).

**Instructions**

For instructions on how to opt out from disclosures of personally identifiable information to companies not owned by mThink who want to market products or services to you, or if you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, please send an email, along with your first and last name, to [info@mthink.com](mailto:info@mthink.com.com).

If you have any questions or concerns about the mThink online policy for this site or its implementation, you may contact us at [info@mthink.com](mailto:info@mthink.com.com).
